{'rapidapi_profile': 'https://rapidapi.com/user/tethertechnologies095',
 'timestamp': '2024-09-21T19:28:40.156Z',
 'triviaQuestions': [{'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'Chapeau',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['Bonnet',
                                            ' &Eacute;charpe',
                                            ' Casque'],
                      'question': 'What is the French word for '
                                  '&quot;hat&quot;?',
                      'type': 'multiple'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'Monty Python',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['The Goodies&lrm;',
                                            'The League of Gentlemen&lrm;',
                                            'The Penny Dreadfuls'],
                      'question': 'Terry Gilliam was an animator that worked '
                                  'with which British comedy group?',
                      'type': 'multiple'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'True',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['False'],
                      'question': 'You can legally drink alcohol while driving '
                                  'in Mississippi.',
                      'type': 'boolean'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'True',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['False'],
                      'question': 'Gumbo is a stew that originated in '
                                  'Louisiana.',
                      'type': 'boolean'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'A dance',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['A medical procedure',
                                            'A sport',
                                            'A language'],
                      'question': 'What is &quot;dabbing&quot;?',
                      'type': 'multiple'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'False',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['True'],
                      'question': 'Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous '
                                  'chemical.',
                      'type': 'boolean'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'True',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['False'],
                      'question': 'Slovakia is a member of European Union-',
                      'type': 'boolean'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'Plum',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['Apple', 'Peach', 'Pear'],
                      'question': 'According to the nursery rhyme, what fruit '
                                  'did Little Jack Horner pull out of his '
                                  'Christmas pie?',
                      'type': 'multiple'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'True',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['False'],
                      'question': '&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer '
                                  'to a list of famous actors, musicians, and '
                                  'artists who died at the age of 27.',
                      'type': 'boolean'},
                     {'category': 'General Knowledge',
                      'correct_answer': 'Pink',
                      'difficulty': 'easy',
                      'incorrect_answers': ['Yellow', 'Blue', 'Green'],
                      'question': 'Which of these colours is NOT featured in '
                                  'the logo for Google?',
                      'type': 'multiple'}]}
